Guide to the Hayne Family Papers1903-2015
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Research Files, 1
  - Montana's Early Soap Industry (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Montana Flouring Mill (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Montana's First Map (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Montana Historic Bridge Inventory (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Montana Map, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Montana Maps – Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
  - Montana Preservation (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Montana Organic Act (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Montana Post (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Montana Prison (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Montana Selective Bibliography (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Montana State Capitol Building (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Mormon Wagon Train (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Mud Brick Houses (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Mullan Road (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Museum of the Plains Indian (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Musselshell County, Montana (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Nebraska Territory, prior to 1861 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Names on the Face of Montana (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Narrow Gauge – Acknowledgements (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Narrow Gauge – Baldwin Locomotives (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Narrow Gauge – Burton Station (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Narrow Gauge – Calgary Book Store (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Narrow Gauge – Cendion Rail (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Narrow Gauge – Cascade Coal Towns (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Narrow Gauge – Changeover Chapter (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Narrow Gauge – Changeover Chapter – Draft (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Narrow Gauge – Changeover Chapter Stories (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Narrow Gauge – Chapter 1 – Early Draft (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Narrow Gauge – Chapter 1 Draft (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Narrow Gauge – Chapter 1 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Narrow Gauge – Chapter 1, Computer Copy (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Narrow Gauge – Collins Station, Original (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Narrow Gauge – Collins Station, Draft (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Narrow Gauge – Collins Station, Early Computer (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Narrow Gauge – Collins Station, Later Computer (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Narrow Gauge – Collins Station Material (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Narrow Gauge – Commencing Operations, Draft (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Narrow Gauge – Commencing Operations, Computer (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Narrow Gauge – Commencing Operations Material (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Narrow Gauge – Conrad Station, Draft (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Narrow Gauge – Conrad Station, Computer (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Narrow Gauge – Construction Chapter (Box 5, Folder 67-73)
  - Narrow Gauge – Correspondences with Stan Gibson (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Narrow Gauge – Dr. Myers (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Narrow Gauge – Duane Olson (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Narrow Gauge – Early Maps (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Narrow Gauge – Early Preface (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Narrow Gauge – Early Story (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Narrow Gauge – Falcon Press (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Narrow Gauge – Fire at Hethbridge (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Narrow Gauge – Freight Info (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Narrow Gauge – Glacier County Historical Society Speech (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Narrow Gauge – Glenbow Museum (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Narrow Gauge – Great Falls GNRHS Convention (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Narrow Gauge – Great Falls Silver Smelter (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Narrow Gauge – Great Falls Tribune Clips (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Narrow Gauge – Incorporation (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Narrow Gauge – Jawbone Railroad (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Narrow Gauge – Kalmbach Library (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lavalle' Book (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge News, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge News, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge News, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge News, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Narrow Gauge – Lethbridge News (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Narrow Gauge – Locomotive Material (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Narrow Gauge – Madeleine Story (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Narrow Gauge – Milk River (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Narrow Gauge – Minnesota Historical Society (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Narrow Gauge – Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Narrow Gauge – Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 1-7)
  - Narrow Gauge – Montana's Narrow Gauge (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Narrow Gauge – Montana's Northern Railroad (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Narrow Gauge – Museum Talk (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Narrow Gauge – Non-Canadian/ G.F. Railroad (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Narrow Gauge – Operations Chapter (Box 6, Folder 12-15)
  - Narrow Gauge – Operations Material (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Narrow Gauge – Police Gazette (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Narrow Gauge – Pondera (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Narrow Gauge – Poor's Manual (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Narrow Gauge – Preface (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Narrow Gauge – Railway History Sources (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Narrow Gauge – Railways of Canada (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Narrow Gauge – Range Fires (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Narrow Gauge – Research (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Narrow Gauge – River Press (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Narrow Gauge – Rocky Springs (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Narrow Gauge – Rolling Stock (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Narrow Gauge – Schedules (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Narrow Gauge – Shelby Chapter (Box 6, Folder 29-31)
  - Narrow Gauge – Shelby Material (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Narrow Gauge – Shelby Opera Story (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Narrow Gauge – Shelby Story (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Narrow Gauge – Sheran Story (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Narrow Gauge – Steell Station (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Narrow Gauge – Steell (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Narrow Gauge – Sweet Grass/ Coutts Stations (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Narrow Gauge – Unloading Facilities (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Narrow Gauge – Willard (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Narrow Gauge – Wrecks (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - National Postal Mark Museum (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Neihart (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Neil Howie (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Newkirk log house – Story (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - New Fort Maginnis (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 47-49)
  - Northern Plains Institute (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - North and South Dakota Squatter Legislatures (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Northwest Centennial (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Northwest Ordinance (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Oil Shale Story (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Old Agency Project (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Old Time Cemetery (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Old Time Woolgrowers (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Ophir, Montana (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Oregon Country (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Oregon Historical Society (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Oregon Territory (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Park County, Montana (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Parson's Bridge (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Pemmican (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Pendroy, Montana (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Perkins Wool Story (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Petroleum County, Montana (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Phillips County, Montana (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Piegan (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Pinkey City, Washington (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Place Name (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Political Cartoons (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Polks Directory Pages (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - Pondera County (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - Pondera County, 1910-1915 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pondera County, 1919; 1929 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Boundary Origins (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Pondera Creation, Original (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Pondera Creation, Later version (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Pondera – First Newspaper Story (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Pondera – Pend d' Oreille (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Pondera – Town (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Powder River County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Powell County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Power State Bank (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Prairie County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Progressive Men of Montana (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Montana Counties (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Ralph Rener Book (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Ravalli County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Reading Brands (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Recipes (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Red River Cart (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Reservations – Blackfeet (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Richland County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - River Press, 1882-1884 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Clippings
  - Road to MacLoed (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Robare – Birch Creek Hanging (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Robare – Buckley, Simons Shooting (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Robare – Father Prando (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Robare – Flory Sullivin's Story (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Robare – Henry Robert (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Robare – Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 29-31)
  - Rocky Mountain Husbandman (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Ron Marlenee (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Roosevelt County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Rosebud County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Sam Sollid (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Sanders County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Sand Cowlee, Montana (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Scrivers – No More Buffalo (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Sellew, William (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Senate Bill 35 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Shelby, Montana (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Shelby Promoter (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Shergold, Montana (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Sheridan County (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Shingle Bolt Drives (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Shoshone County (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Shuler Grizzly Bears (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Silver Bow County (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Simpson, Montana (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Skagway, Alaska (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Skamania County (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - South Dakota Historical Society (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Spokane County (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Society out in Montana (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - South Pass City, Wyoming (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Stagecoach (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Stage Lines (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Stanford, Montana (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Steamboats on the upper Missouri (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Steilacoom Farm (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Stillwater County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - St. Mary's Canal (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Story of the Magic Keg (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - St. Peter's Mission (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Sun River, Montana (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Swift Current (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Swift Dam Flood (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Sweet Grass County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - Sweet Grass Hills (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - Sweet Grass Hills – Mining (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Taft, Montana (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Telephones in the Early Days (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Teton County Centennial (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Teton County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Toole County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Treasure County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Turbulent Days in county affairs (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Two Dot, Montana (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - U.S. Territory Maps (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Valley County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Valier, Montana (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Valier – American Legion (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Valier – Belgian Colony (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - Valier- Double Killings (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - Valier Methodist Church (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - Vancouver County (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - Vaughn Homestead (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Violence in America (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - Vlidia, Montana (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - Whacky Words (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - Wagner, Montana (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Walla Walla County (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - Water Rights (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - Water Wagons – Wagon Trains (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - Wheatland County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - White Sulphur Spring (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Whoop Up Trail (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - Whoop Up Trail – Maps (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - Wibaux County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - Wilderness Study Summary (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - Williams, Montana (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - Wolf Management (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - Woodhawks (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - W.W. DeLacy (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Wyoming Territory (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Yellowstone Buffalo, 1930 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - Yellowstone County, Montana (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Yukon (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - Zortman, Montana (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Dupuyer Social Club, 2
  The Dupuyer Social Club was a leading community influencer in Dupuyer and the surrounding areas. The club held picnics, ran Community Theater and administered news about the town and its members in a weekly newsletter. Harriett Hayne was a leading member of the club and help organize many of the projects the club participated in. This includes minute books, financial records and newsletters sponsored by the club. Photos related to this series are numbers: 73-75.
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Anderson Mercantile Newsletter and Menu, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Anderson Mercantile Newsletter and Menu, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Anderson Mercantile Newsletter and Menu, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Finances and Bills (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Hiway Café Newsletter and Menu, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Hiway Café Newsletter and Menu, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Hiway Café Newsletter and Menu, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (October 1947 – November 1949) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (November 1949 – December 1951) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (January 1952 – December 1954) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (January 1955 – December 1956) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (January 1957 – February 1958) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (March 1958 – May 1960) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (June 1960 – January 1962) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (February 1962 – December 1963) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Minutes, (January 1964 – November 1967) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Dupuyer Social Club – Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Political Papers, 3
  Harriett Hayne served as a state representative for Montana for almost twenty years. This collection contains papers and articles relating to her political career. Legislative reports and articles, bills, and programs she worked on are included. Located in the flat box, there are election materials and signs relating to her time in office as well. Photos related to this series are numbers: 76-85.
  - Aging and Health Events, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - American Legion Auxiliary Speech (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Ballots (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Big Horn County Republican Women's Club (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Bill HB485 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Certificate – Election School, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Certificate – Election, 1984/1985 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Certificate – Recognition, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Certificate – Nomination (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Certificate – U.S. Flag, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Clinton (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - The Commonwealth Parliamentary Association 29th Regional Conference (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Girls State Yearbooks (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Girls State, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Girls State, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - GOP Handbooks (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - House and Senate Assembly Seating (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - House Bills (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - House Daily Status Reports (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - House Hearing Schedules (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - House Journals (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Inauguration State, State of State Message, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Jack Hayne – Reports Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Ledgers (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Legislative Articles (Box 9, Folder 25-31)
  - Legislative Memorial Service (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Legislative Reports (Box 9, Folder 33-39)
  - Legislative Report Transcripts (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Letters – Legislative, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Letters – Legislative, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Letter to the Editor (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Letter to the Editor – Jack Hayne (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1980/1985 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Lists of Registered Electors in Pondera County (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Memorial Day Talk, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Montana Election Results (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Montana Farm Bureau Federation (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Montana Historical Society (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Montana Political Divisions (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Montana Republican Party Committees (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Montana Republican Party Rules, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Montana State Representatives Election, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Montana School Board Association (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Montana Water Court (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - News Items on Harriet Hayne (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
  - Pondera Republicans (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Portrait of Harriet Hayne (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Resume, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Sales Tax Report (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Senate Journals (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Speech Note Cards (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Taft – Hartley Act (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Tri County Cow Belles (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Voter Opinion Survey (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Water Rights Report, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Harriett Hayne objects (Box 15)
    The Flat box contains various objects pertaining to Harriette Hayne's political career and achievements. Including posters, campaign materials and various awards and plaques for her service to the state of Montana and the Republican Party.
- Correspondence, 1903-2012; Series 4
  Letters sent by various members of the Hayne family to friends, family and colleagues. The letters are sorted by date written and sent.
  - 1903 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 1906 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - 1908 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - 1921 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - 1928 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - 1932 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - 1936 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - 1937 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 1938 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - 1939 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - 1942 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - 1943 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - 1944 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - 1945 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - January 14–March 6, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - March 7–21, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - March 22–December 11, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 1947 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - 1948 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - 1949 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 1950 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - 1951 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - 1952 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - 1953 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - 1954 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - 1956 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 1958 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - 1959 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - 1960 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - 1961 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - 1962 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - 1963 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - 1964 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - 1965 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - 1966 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - 1967 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - 1968 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - 1969 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - 1970 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - 1974 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - 1977 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - 1981 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - 1982 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - 1983 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - 1984 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - 1985 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - 1986 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - 1987 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - 1988 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - 1989 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - 1990 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - 1991 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - 1992 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - 1993 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - 1994 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - 1995 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - 1996 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - 1997 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - 1998 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - 1999 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - 2000 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - 2001 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - 2002 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - 2003 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - 2004 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - 2005 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - 2007 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - 2008 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - 2009 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - 2012 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Unknown Dates (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Personal Papers, 5
  Documents, pamphlets, articles, letters, greeting cards and certificates that deal with the personal aspect of the Hayne family. Topics like family histories, school records, and military service records represent a majority of the collection, however personal property deeds and certificate can be found here as well. Photos related to this series are numbers: 86-258.
  - Address Book (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Autograph Book (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Baby Announcements (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Baptism Certificate (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Birth Certificates (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Branding Papers (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Certificates (Box 12, Folder 7)
    (Farm)
  - Certificate (Box 12, Folder 8)
    (High Frontier)
  - Certificate (Box 12, Folder 9)
    (Live Insurance)
  - Certificate (Box 12, Folder 10)
    (Sun River Electorate Co-Op)
  - Certificate (Box 12, Folder 11)
    (4-H Leadership)
  - Check Records (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Date Book – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Drivers Licenses (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Dupuyer 8th Grade Graduation, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Finch Farms (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Gifts (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Girl Scouts – Mary Haynes (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Graduation Speeches – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Graduation Talk, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Jack Hayne
  - Gray's Harbor Junior College – Jack Hayne (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Greeting Cards (Box 12, Folder 22-29)
  - Hayne Family History (Box 12, Folder 30-33)
  - Hayne – Hayne Daily (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Hayne Reunion, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - High School 50th Reunion (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Jack Hayne's 80th (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Lewis and Clark Advisory Council Appointment (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Marriage License – Jack and Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - McVicar Family History (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Membership Cards (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Memorial Items – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Memorial Item – Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Miller Clipper Yearbooks (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Montana Historical Society board of Trustees appointment (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Music Items – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Newspaper Clippings – Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Old Currency (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - High School Memories – Palmer (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Photos of Effie Hayne (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Photos of George Roy Hayne (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Prize Ribbons – Effie Hayne (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - School Work – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - School Work – Jack Hayne (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Trip Diary's (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - US Army Certificates – George Roy Hayne (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - US Marine Corps – Enlistment (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - US Marine Corps – Journal (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - US Marine Corps – Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - US Marine Corps – Separation Papers (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - US Navy – Certificate (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - US Navy – Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 62-65)
  - US Navy – Separation Papers (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Wadsworth High School Commencement (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Wahkiakum County High School – Harriet Hayne (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Wedding Invitations/Announcements (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Photographs, Albums, and Ephemra, Series 6
  The photo albums were labeled by physical description and grouped by content. The content ranges from the Hayne's personal military service to Harriett's political career. Loose photographs were identified, sorted into groups that correspond with pervious series in the collection and filed into group folders. Oversized images have been separated and moved to an oversized location. Folders with separating notices are marked with an asterisk(*).
  - American Legion Auxiliary Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Navy Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - United States Navy Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Personal Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Personal Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 5)
    (Wood Cover)
  - Red Photo Album (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Blue covered scrapbook – Political Career Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Black Photographs Book (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Tru-line Notebook – Fashion Scrapbook (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cattle, Hogs, Sheep Mini-journal – Finance Book (Box 13, Folder 10)